(Howard:)Then she said,
"Do you not want me to come?"
(Howard:)Then I bought her a new laptop
and the game...
...and she's parking the car now.
ls the whip-sound app
contextually appropriate here?
Uh, it is, but I think you might have
waited too long for it to be funny.
- l was wrong. It's still funny.
- Oh, good.
(Leonard:)Oh.
- Amy, what's wrong?
- My boyfriend's a jerk.
(Penny:)Well, I know he didn't cheat on you,
so, what happened?
l had to go to my aunt's party by myseIf.
Everybody was like, "where's this
boyfriend you talk about? Ls he real?
(Amy:)Or did you make him up like Armin
the miniature-horse breeder?"
Who's Armin the miniature-horse breeder?
(Amy:)The pretend boyfriend I invented
to get my family off my back.